

# Parvindra Tongar (UI/UX Designer)

User Experience, User-Centred Design, Interaction Design, Startups Figma, Sketch, Photoshop, Framer | Wireframes, Prototypes, User-flow HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Angular UI | Responsive Web Design

# **CONTACT**

Mobile: +91-7428098010 Email: parvtongar@gmail.com

# **EDUCATION**

# **Post Graduation (2009)**

Aptech ACCP(Web Design and Development)

#### **Graduation (2007)**

Bachelor of Arts (CCS University)

# **PROFILE SUMMARY**

Designer with **10+ years** of overall experience and 5+ years of experience in UX Design and have experience working with startups and Big Organisations as an Individual designer as well as team of designer.

I have very good experience in following quick design approach to start a project and serve it with the client with a short period of time and finalise it.

I have good design experience in Web Application, Admin Panels and Mobile-based designs from paper sketch to interconnect screens prototypes.

#### **PROJECTS**

## **CurrencyEx, 12 Weeks (Currently Working...)**

An application that allowed for business-to-business foreign currency and same-currency payments

# MovTek, 24 Weeks

MovTek provides Air and Sea Freight services across the globe.

## **Hire Military Jobs, 24 Weeks**

This project helps Retired Military persons to find new jobs in corporates and other internal screens have been done like Admin-panel.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Apr 2016 to Present

# Lead Designer at Nuage Biztech pvt Itd

I have worked on multi-domain Web and Mobile Apps. have versatile experience in Designing Admin Panels, Web Apps and Websites.

May 2013 to Oct 2015

## Website Designer at Rati software solutions

Website Designer, Responsive Design, Web Designer, HTML Coder, Slicing - Photoshop to HTML.

Aug 2008 to May 2013

## **Website Designer at ekant solutions**

Website Designer, Web Designer, HTML5, CSS3, Slicing - Photoshop to HTML.